bidz.com 2007-12-12

# Bidz.com - Online Jewelry Auctions. Shop for diamond jewelry, engagement rings, designer watches, and much more.

**_Information collected on Bidz.com will not be sold, shared or rented to others._**

Order Form

Bidz.com requires information from customers on our order form. Here customers must provide contact information (like name and shipping address) and financial information (like credit card number, expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill customer's orders. If we have trouble processing an order, this contact information is used to get in touch with a customer. 

Cookies

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the customer's hard drive containing information about the user. For instance, by setting a cookie on our site, users will not have to provide address details each time they order and the view my orders screen can remember products purchased at an earlier time. Cookies are stored on the customer's computer only. We have no access to their content.

Log Files

We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

Links

This page may contain links to other sites. Please be aware that Bidz.com does not control or affirm the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by Bidz.com 

Security

Bidz.com takes every precaution to protect our users' information. When our registration/order form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number and/or social security number), that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software in the industry.

Notification of Changes

If Bidz.com decide to change our privacy policy, Bidz.com will post those changes on our Homepage so our users are always aware of what information Bidz.com collect, how Bidz.com use it, and under circumstances, if any, Bidz.com disclose it. If at any point Bidz.com decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, Bidz.com will notify users by way of an email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not Bidz.com use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected. 

Other

We reserve the right to repeat comments about our products made in communications with us for marketing purposes.
